

NAY THI YEN

Pharmacist

- **15/08/1992**
- Female
- 0964863683
- naythiyenydh@gmail.com
- Number 606/97, 3/2 street, ward 14, district 10, HCM city

SUMMARY

After 3 years as a medical representative, I look forward to working as a professional. I can apply the knowledge learned to take care of patients and protect holistically their health . Learning, improving knowledge and I want to work in a good environment to dedicate myself and endure for a long time, contributing to the development of the hospital.

SKILLS

Software: Microsoft Office

Languages: English

Social skills: Communication skills. Being able to work under stress.



WHAT I CAN DO WELL

- Ability to learn and memorize very quickly.
- Good consulting and convicing skills, aware of customer needs.
- Work diligently and meticulously.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SANOFI-AVENTIS VIETNAM COMPANY

SEP 2016 - NOW

Medical Representative

- Establish and develop good relationships with key opinion leaders, doctors and pharmacists.
- Do SMART calls with doctors.
- Plan strategies to increase sales.
- Achieve over 100% target, growth over 200%.
- Supply medical information to doctors.

GENERAL HOSPITAL GIA LAI PROVINCE

JUN 2016 - SEP 2016

Pharmacist

- Distrubute medicines for inpatient.
- Track amount of medicines in storage frequently.
- Guide to safe, reasonable, effective and economical using of drugs.



EDUCATION

HUE UNIVERSITY OF PHARMACY AND MEDICINE

SEP 2011 - JUL 2016

Pharmacist

- GPA 7.35
- Got ADB scholarship.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certification of office computer: Level B

2016

- Certificate of achiverment for national English: Level C

2016